Essentially
They formed an agreement
Not to mention
things that were obviously wrong with the project.
They kind of formed an agreement to kind of keep quiet about things that were problematic about a project. So the project will get moving, and it would
It would happen, basically
The people who are involved. So like the people who are managing the projects onto the projects happen, the people working on the projects wanted the projects to happen
And the hiding hand is a kind of it's an economist's pun, so it's not very funny. But it's basically kind of like play on the words of
The guiding hand, which is Adam Smith's idea that
Adam Smith's idea that when I did this, when I did this, I did a talk like this two years ago in Edinburgh, and I could mention that Adam Smith had a statue just down the road
in Edinburgh, famous Scottish economist, and he had the idea that
That prices
appear through the kind of invisible effort of lots and lots and lots of different people. So kind of prices rise and they fall through what what what Adam Smith called the guiding hand. And so
Hirschman is basically saying there's a kind of similar kind of thing, which is all of these people are involved in the projects. They don't get together and have a meeting and decide not to mention what's wrong with the project